export const structure = [
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "Amanda Way's career as a social reformer ___ in 1851 when, at an antislavery meeting in Indiana, she called for a state woman's rights convention.",
        "options": [
            "begin",
            "began",
            "have begun",
            "to have begun"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "The celesta, an orchestral percussion instrument, resembles ___.",
        "options": [
            "a small upright piano",
            "how a small upright piano",
            "a small upright piano is",
            "as a small upright piano"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "Thomas Paine, ___, wrote Common Sense, a pamphlet that identified the American colonies with the cause of liberty.",
        "options": [
            "writer of eloquent",
            "whose eloquent writing",
            "an eloquent writer",
            "writing eloquent"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "Although beavers rarely remain submerged for more than two minutes, they can stay underwater ___ fifteen minutes before having to surface for air.",
        "options": [
            "as long",
            "as long as",
            "so long",
            "so long that"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "Protein digestion begins in the stomach ___ ends in the small intestine.",
        "options": [
            "while",
            "and",
            "how",
            "because"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "When natural gas burns, its ___ into atoms of carbon and hydrogen.",
        "options": [
            "hydrocarbon molecules, breaking up",
            "broke up by hydrocarbon molecules",
            "hydrocarbon molecules break up",
            "broken up hydrocarbon molecules"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "___ ballet dancers learn five basic positions for the arms and feet.",
        "options": [
            "All of",
            "Of every",
            "All",
            "Every"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "Some colonies of bryozoans, small marine animals, form ___ with trailing stems.",
        "options": [
            "creeping colonies",
            "which colonies creep",
            "creeping colonies are",
            "colonies creep"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg argued six women's rights cases before the United States Supreme Court in the 1970's, ___.",
        "options": [
            "of five winning them",
            "five winning of them",
            "of them five winning",
            "winning five of them"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "Natural selection is defined as the process ___ the course of evolution by preserving those traits best adapted for an organism's survival.",
        "options": [
            "to which directs",
            "of which directs it",
            "directs it",
            "that directs"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "___ 363 miles between the cities of Albany and Buffalo in New York State, the Erie Canal helped link the Atlantic Ocean with the Great Lakes.",
        "options": [
            "The extension of",
            "The extension",
            "Extending",
            "Extends"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "The chief sources of B12, a water-soluble vitamin ___ stored in the body, include meat, milk and eggs.",
        "options": [
            "is not",
            "that is not",
            "not that is",
            "that not"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "___ is rooted in experiments in iron and steel conducted in the nineteenth century.",
        "options": [
            "While the history of twentieth-century architecture",
            "The history of twentieth-century architecture",
            "That the history of twentieth-century architecture",
            "Both twentieth-century architecture and its history"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "The primary source of energy for tropical cyclones is the latent heat released when ___.",
        "options": [
            "does water vapor condense",
            "condensed water vapor",
            "water vapor condenses",
            "the condensation of water vapor"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "type": "structure",
        "question": "Manufacturing is Canada's most important economic activity, ___ 17 percent of the workforce.",
        "options": [
            "engages",
            "and to engage",
            "that it engage",
            "engaging"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    }
]